hello friends in this video let's look
at how to buy equity using your I see I
see a direct account and on your phone
so I have downloaded the ICAC director
and this is the screen that I get on
logging in now if you see on the top
left-hand corner you'll get the various
menu options like home trading in the
strike your investment market research
and at your service to buy equity just
click on trade and invest so out here
there are various ways in which you can
go either you can straightaway go and
allocate funds or you can go to equity
I'll go to equity first now there are
various options related to equity
whether you want to buy equity through
cash you want to sell equity through
cash you want to get a code you want to
do a margin by and a lot of other things
that you can see out here there are also
options of portfolio order book etc that
you can use but for the simplicity of
this video let's concentrate on how to
buy equity using the ICS a direct app so
you click on cash buy on the next page
you'll get the various options that you
need to populate for buying the stock
that you want so under product there are
two options cash and flexy cash I'll
keep it as cash the exchanges say NSE
National Stock Exchange is the stock
exchange from which you want to buy that
companies are shares so I let's take for
this example I see a bank
so under stock if you start typing the
name say I see I then you can see that
already it has been populated but let's
try one more a little bit and I see I
see a bank is appearing here on the pop
you just selected here you can mention
the quantity so let's say you want to
buy 10 shares the diet the order
tee's mentioned out here whether it's a
day order an IOC or a VDC let's keep it
as day order type is market or limit if
you set limit then you can specify the
price at which you want to buy this a
share say you specify 282 is the price
at which you will buy the share if it is
anything beyond 282 you wouldn't be
buying it if its market on the other
hand and you do not get the option to
enter any amount whatever is the correct
current price of the share is the amount
at which you'll have to buy it so that's
it that those are the mandatory fees
that you need to buy shares if you click
on buy now you'll go to the next page
and on that it will you'll be prompted
with a question whether you want to add
funds to buy this share or if there are
funds already allocated then you won't
have to do anything so that's it friends
it's as easy as this to buy shares using
I see I see a direct app thanks for
watching